{
    
        "questions": [
          {"prompt": "5 * 10 = ", "answer": 50},
          {"prompt": "45 + 23 = ", "answer": 68},
          {"prompt": "8 * 7 = ", "answer": 56},
          {"prompt": "12 - 4 = ", "answer": 8},
          {"prompt": "100 / 5 = ", "answer": 20},
          {"prompt": "15 + 35 = ", "answer": 50},
          {"prompt": "9 * 6 = ", "answer": 54},
          {"prompt": "25 - 13 =", "answer": 12},
          {"prompt": "64 / 8 = ", "answer": 8},
          {"prompt": "30 + 40 = ", "answer": 70}
        ]
      }
      
